on April 21st 2023 I made a hundred ten
thousand dollars under 24 hours with my
simple trading strategy I literally told
everybody on my social media Discord
Instagram Instagram story I even like
texted my accent or not and the
following minutes I'm going to show you
exactly how I did this very simple but
before we get started I have a video
where it teaches you from scratch how to
make your first hundred thousand dollars
a thousand dollars so then you can
eventually scale to 110 000 like I did
all you have to do is just click this
video up here it's a very simple way to
teach you from scratch but before we
start I want to show you guys that this
is a real account you guys can see all
of the trades that I took here deposit
withdraws the exact hundred thousand
dollar trades other trades that I have
lost other trades that I have one just
to show you guys how legit this strategy
is and to show you guys if I did it so
can you guys so I want you guys
understand how I manifested this as
crazy as that might sound I woke up on a
Sunday and when I look at the market
something just looks so picture perfect
that I have seen it in the past but I
just wanted to trade a little bit more
aggressive this week and I literally
posted it in my Discord my free telegram
I made a whole Instagram post about it
I'm like guys you guys are going to see
at the end of the week I'm going to make
a hundred thousand dollars little did I
know that was waiting ahead of me was a
140 000 a week so I overachieved that
making this my new goal to begin with I
want to explain a simple philosophy when
it comes to my training simplest way I
can put it is trading is just like
surfing so let's say you're a surfer
your goal is to go out to the beach get
on a wave and just ride the wave all the
way to the short your goal as a Trader
is to come to the computer get in the
markets and ride the wave whether the
Market's going up or ride the way where
the market is going down it is the same
thing so the first thing you do when
you're a surfer when you get to the
beach you have to look outside see if
there's waves if there's waves you go
into the water and then you surf them so
as a Trader the first thing you do when
you come to the market is you sit down
the computer you look at the market of
the trend and you identify if it's going
up or if it's going down if you properly
can't identify whether it's going up or
going down you're already making the
first mistake as a Trader so the first
step is to identify the trend when you
come into the market so essentially the
Market's going down I'm looking for
sales and the Market's going up I'm
looking for buys and in this case the
market was all bearish every single time
frame was headed to the downside so I
was just looking for a very simple and
specific point to hop in on that wave to
just keep going to the downside and this
was actually a very clear and simple
trade and I'm going to tell you guys
exactly why I'm going to tell you guys
through the very moment where I realized
it's going to be a high probability
trade setup that was going to give me
the hundred thousand dollars in one
trading day right so before we get into
the charts this is going to be very
similar like surfing yes like literally
writing a wave actual surfing so when
you are going to the beach and let's
suppose you are a surfer your goal is to
catch a wave and then you're supposed to
make it all the way to the short so this
is you here stick figure my best version
of stick figure drawing for your
surfboard and your goal is to make it
all the way to the beach so let's say
this is the beach this is version of a
palm tree and then your beach chair so
on right you understand your goal is to
get at the top of the wave so you make
it all the way to the short we kind of
have the same thing when it comes to
trading but our goal is to ride our
trade to our take profit our goal is to
take our trade to make it to where we
want to get out so before you get to the
beach your first thing is to see are the
waves coming north or are they going
south basically in simple terms are the
waves going this way or are the waves
going this way what waves are the waves
going because that way you can obviously
know where to write it it is the same
thing when we come to the markets the
first thing you got to do is identify is
the market going up or is the market
going down so very similar how a wave
moves like this to the upside a wave can
move like this to the downside whether
it's going north whether it's going
south so when we first get to this
Market we can identify that these waves
were going to the upside at one point
and then after it kept going to the
upside then the wave started going to
the downside right if you were to just
look at this Market simple in a way
perspective you can see here how this
Market was heading to the north side and
then after it basically broke out and
you can see how then the markets are now
heading to the South Side so this is the
simplest way how I can get you to
visualize the waves going up or the
waves going down so my first rule my
first Confluence when I come into
trading is I need to understand what are
the waves doing are the waves going up
or are the waves going down in Market
terms is the trend bullish or is the
trend bearish so I first identify this
on the weekly daily four-hour time
frames to understand is the market going
up or is the market going down after we
identify whether the market is going up
or going down I then ask myself are we
rejecting area of interest for me to get
in and this zone right here is my area
of Interest very similar like if you
were to be riding a wave is am I
entering the wave at the beginning of it
am I entering at the middle of it where
am I entering the wig am I like this guy
right now where he's at the bottom of
the wave or am I like this guy right
here where he is at the top of the wave
and this is also known in training
perspective as area of Interest so after
I identify that we are clearly waving to
the downside then I realized all right
this point right here is the top of the
wave at the Zone where I want to get in
after we identify this that leads to my
third point which obviously we have a
total of nine which we're going to look
at every single one of them which gives
me the exact reasoning on why I took
this trade the third one would be what
is my entry signal and wave perspective
what is indicating to me that I am ready
to get on this wave so to give an
example of what a entry signal is when
it comes to trading it is Candlestick
rejections we have these rejection
candlesticks all throughout the charts
it might look like a lot to understand
at one point but you can tell this is a
very strong moving Candlestick versus
these candlesticks are just stopped this
is because these candlesticks are
rejecting and this is just moving
towards like the weight so to put it in
a simple perspective like a wave is
before you get on any wave you can see
all these Bubbles and all these uh white
stuff happening at the top of the wave
that is giving you the indication that
the wave is about to crash and head to
the downside that is your entry signal
to get on the wave and this is very
similar on any single type of wave you
are getting on so before I get to the
market I need an entry signal so as you
can tell right here we have this is
called a doji Candlestick so a doji
Candlestick is part of my rules to take
a trade because it is required for an
entry signal after my injury signal I
then need a bearish confirmation that we
are rejecting this zone so after the
scene the first bubbles come on to the
Chart where I essentially am getting the
notification that the wave is coming
down this is my first bubble indication
that this move is heading to the
downside so after this first bubble I
needed to be what is called a rejection
bearish engulfing which is this
Candlestick record so both of these
right here this is called a doji and
then this is called a bearish
Candlestick formation if you've never
seen these type of candlesticks before
there's a free book down below where
it's called the Japanese Candlestick
Bible it's a trading book that I read
it's like 20 30 pages long in every
single picture that's a brief
description of what every single
Candlestick is and it is very simple to
read the markets after you read this
book this is simple as reading a Pre-K
book because it's just a picture and a
brief description so this is going to
help you understand that this is my
entry signal to enter the wave I have to
understand what the entry signal is this
is where then I will where am I getting
out of this way because before you get
on to the wave you need to understand
where am I getting off am I going to get
on the wave at this point and it's my
goal to ride it all the way to shore
it's my goal to get on this wave and
make it all the way to the Rocks where
are you trying to ride the wave to so
this is where you need to understand
that you need to set an area where the
wave ends where the wave is just going
to crash and then you are done so this
is very similar in this trade and the
way I identify where I'm going to get
out of the wave is by looking for the
next Zone where it is considered support
and resistance another spot where a wave
has rejected in the past which is also
known as structure points like these
levels right here if you notice we have
one
two three four rejections so this is
basically an area where the wave it can
potentially make it and then crash
before coming back up and then creating
another wave heading to the downside so
this is the spot where I realize well
I understand that this is an area where
the wave can make it and this is very
key because a lot of surfers a mistake
they can make is that they can want to
ride the wave past the short you can't
ride the wave past the short and in
trading this is a huge mistake Traders
want to hold the trade past their take
profit if this right here is your entry
point and this would be your stop loss
this would have to be a take profit and
that is it this is where a lot of
Traders get greedy and they make the
mistake thinking they can ride the way
forever you can't ride the weight
forever so after we understand where
we're going to get out this is where I
would understand what am I risking
trade what am I risking on this point so
whenever I take a trade I risk anywhere
from one to three percent of my account
so this is where I would go to a
position size calculator and be like
what am I going to risk on this trade so
let's say for instance your account
balance is a hundred thousand dollars
whether it's a challenge or whether it
is a personal con that you are trading
and you want to risk a one percent of
your account and then let's say you just
want to have a let's say for this
example we had a 24 pip stop loss you
don't know what Pips is it is point in
percentage there's no reason for you to
calculate it these things do it for you
so we're going to put a 24 pip stop loss
on nzd USD which was the pair that we
were trading after you understand that
this is the pair you click calculate and
this literally tells you how many Lots
so you should put on your trade meaning
you're only risking one thousand dollars
on this trade to put it into the wave
example before you get onto the way if
you need to ask yourself is this wave
worth getting wet or falling off the
wave and hurting myself like you just
need to understand the risk you're
taking before you are taking this trip
so after I did all of this stuff
understand that the waves or the trend
is going to the downside understanding
that we're rejecting my area of Interest
understanding where I'm getting out
where why am I getting in and what I'm
risking this is where I'm like you know
what okay it is time at this point it's
time to get in the trade in the wave I
hope you guys like this wave analogy
it's like super simple and very
relatable so this is why I said okay
let's take the trade this is where I go
to my meditator 4 meditator five
whatever's best for you guys you place
the trade and then you set and forget
what is set and forget you have to let
the trade go all the way to your take
profit and that is it your goal is to
get off at Short you don't want to get
off the wave before you get to the shore
doesn't look cool it wasn't worth the
risk that you took initially so after
this point that I get on the way wave
this is where I literally just this is
where I show all my friends that I'm on
the way like this would literally be me
right here like hey I'm on the wave I
just got on everything is lining up
perfectly in trading examples where I
would post a trade on Instagram my
telegram my Discord and be like hey guys
this is the trade this is the trade
that's going to give me the hundred
thousand dollars so while we're in that
trade in the middle of the wave I was
debating whether I should get on or get
off or keep writing it because we were
somewhere in the middle like this and I
was probably already up around fifty
thousand dollars and I'm like you know
what like this is enough right obviously
it's not my hundred thousand dollar goal
but I'm halfway there and realistically
this is almost as big as my last biggest
trade-in day only one in the morning
and I'm debating [__] I close right now
on the tree we saw a little bit more I
can close right now and call it 100K a
week
where
greed kicks in
but this is where I stuck to my
philosophy upset and forget and what set
of forget means is you just set your
trade and you forget how long for it to
get there because that way you will hold
yourself accountable for sticking to
your trading rules which is getting off
at Short your goal as a surfer is to
make it all the way back to the shore
like this guy right here so you rode the
wave all the way back to shore you're
going to not get off in the middle of
the way that is not a successful surfing
day and not a successful trade
power upset and [__]
thank you
[Music]
because I gotta close this damn trade
we are good
so after the trade plays out if you guys
realize this is where I pretty much just
went to sleep put my phone down and when
I woke up the next day my tree had hit
my take profit and this is where I go on
Instagram show everybody post it make a
huge post about it for me it was a very
big deal because I would never make this
at my old job working probably five
years back to back saving every single
dollar so the fact that I made it in
just one shop probably a little under 24
hours is a very very big deal to me and
you guys can see here in the date below
this is April 21st 2023 on a Friday so
the market closes on Friday this train
hit my take profit right on Friday which
was perfect because that is the right
time for me to withdraw the money right
after work and this is how I made the
hundred ten thousand dollars in just one
simple trading day I know it might be
too simple with the analogy that I was
putting with the ways but that is really
how simple it is trading should not be
complicated at all I go through my
series of confluences my series of
reasons on why I'm taking the trade and
this is what my Center forget strategy
is literally anyone can do it you're
going to believe in what I'm saying you
could just really come to your own
conclusions but what is the link in the
description you will find out something
that can work for you because if it did
it for me it can also do it for you if
you guys found this video useful make
sure to drop a comment if you guys like
the simple wave analogy and how uh you
know unique I made it make sure to drop
it in the comments hit the like And
subscribe button and I will see you guys
in the next video guys